Guide to the Richard Foreman and Kate Manheim Papers MSS.152
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIV: Media
  - Subseries B: Sound Effects - Originals
    - Title: Slo March / Hi Sop (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2099)
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Smooth Swoop / B's; Waddle; Sop Hit / Bop; Piano; Disco - Baratone; 3 Bt. / Thud 4; Sop Lub; Claxl; Rota fog; Schubert Sing; T.D. / Pogo
    - Title: Smooth Swoop / B's (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2100)
      Related ID's: 152.2097-152.2099; 152.2101-152.2110
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Slo March / Hi Sop; Waddle; Sop Hit / Bop; Piano; Disco - Baratone; 3 Bt. / Thud 4; Sop Lub; Claxl; Rota fog; Schubert Sing; T.D. / Pogo
    - Title: Waddle (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2101)
      Related ID's: 152.2097-152.2100; 152.2102-152.2110
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Slo March / Hi Sop; Smooth Swoop / B's; Sop Hit / Bop; Piano; Disco - Baratone; 3 Bt. / Thud 4; Sop Lub; Claxl; Rota fog; Schubert Sing; T.D. / Pogo
    - Title: Sop Hit / Bop (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2102)
      Related ID's: 152.2097-152.2101; 152.2103-152.2110
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Slo March / Hi Sop; Smooth Swoop / B's; Waddle; Piano; Disco - Baratone; 3 Bt. / Thud 4; Sop Lub; Claxl; Rota fog; Schubert Sing; T.D. / Pogo
    - Title: Piano (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2103)
      Related ID's: 152.2097-152.2102; 152.2104-152.2110
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Slo March / Hi Sop; Smooth Swoop / B's; Waddle; Sop Hit / Bop; Disco - Baratone; 3 Bt. / Thud 4; Sop Lub; Claxl; Rota fog; Schubert Sing; T.D. / Pogo
    - Title: Disco - Baratone (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2104)
      Related ID's: 152.2097-152.2103; 152.2105-152.2110
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Slo March / Hi Sop; Smooth Swoop / B's; Waddle; Sop Hit / Bop; Piano; 3 Bt. / Thud 4; Sop Lub; Claxl; Rota fog; Schubert Sing; T.D. / Pogo
    - Title: 3 Bt. / Thud 4 (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2105)
      Related ID's: 152.2097-152.2104; 152.2106-152.2110
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Slo March / Hi Sop; Smooth Swoop / B's; Waddle; Sop Hit / Bop; Piano; Disco - Baratone; Sop Lub; Claxl; Rota fog; Schubert Sing; T.D. / Pogo
    - Title: Sop Lub (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2106)
      Related ID's: 152.2097-152.2105; 152.2107-152.2110
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Slo March / Hi Sop; Smooth Swoop / B's; Waddle; Sop Hit / Bop; Piano; Disco - Baratone; 3 Bt. / Thud 4; Claxl; Rota fog; Schubert Sing; T.D. / Pogo
    - Title: Claxl (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2107)
      Related ID's: 152.2097-152.2106; 152.2108-152.2110
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Slo March / Hi Sop; Smooth Swoop / B's; Waddle; Sop Hit / Bop; Piano; Disco - Baratone; 3 Bt. / Thud 4; Sop Lub; Rota fog; Schubert Sing; T.D. / Pogo
    - Title: Rota fog (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2108)
      Related ID's: 152.2097-152.2107; 152.2109-152.2110
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Slo March / Hi Sop; Smooth Swoop / B's; Waddle; Sop Hit / Bop; Piano; Disco - Baratone; 3 Bt. / Thud 4; Sop Lub; Claxl; Schubert Sing; T.D. / Pogo
    - Title: Schubert Sing (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2109)
      Related ID's: 152.2097-152.2108; 152.2110
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Slo March / Hi Sop; Smooth Swoop / B's; Waddle; Sop Hit / Bop; Piano; Disco - Baratone; 3 Bt. / Thud 4; Sop Lub; Claxl; Rota fog; T.D. / Pogo
      Tape Brand: Sony Type I (Normal) Position Normal Bias HF-S
    - Title: T.D. / Pogo (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2110)
      Related ID's: 152.2097-152.2109
      Related Titles: Ring; Tweek fast; Slo March / Hi Sop; Smooth Swoop / B's; Waddle; Sop Hit / Bop; Piano; Disco - Baratone; 3 Bt. / Thud 4; Sop Lub; Claxl; Rota fog; Schubert Sing
    - Title: Latin (L) (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2111)
      Related ID's: 152.2112-152.2117
      Related Titles: W Long Ravish; H Jazy (B: Scissors); Sax Moan; Fun (A: Drumly / Pleasure); Dont No / Pump Chaw; Piano Trip
    - Title: W Long Ravish (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2112)
      Related ID's: 152.2111; 152.2113-152.2117
      Related Titles: Latin (L); H Jazy (B: Scissors); Sax Moan; Fun (A: Drumly / Pleasure); Dont No / Pump Chaw; Piano Trip
    - Title: H Jazy (B: Scissors) (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2113)
      Related ID's: 152.2111-152.2112; 152.2114-152.2117
      Related Titles: Latin (L); W Long Ravish; Sax Moan; Fun (A: Drumly / Pleasure); Dont No / Pump Chaw; Piano Trip
    - Title: Sax Moan (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2114)
      Related ID's: 152.2111-152.2113; 152.2115-152.2117
      Related Titles: Latin (L); W Long Ravish; H Jazy (B: Scissors); Fun (A: Drumly / Pleasure); Dont No / Pump Chaw; Piano Trip
    - Title: Fun (A: Drumly / Pleasure) (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2115)
      Related ID's: 152.2111-152.2114; 152.2116-152.2117
      Related Titles: Latin (L); W Long Ravish; H Jazy (B: Scissors); Sax Moan; Dont No / Pump Chaw; Piano Trip
    - Title: Dont No / Pump Chaw (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2116)
      Related ID's: 152.2111-152.2115; 152.2117
      Related Titles: Latin (L); W Long Ravish; H Jazy (B: Scissors); Sax Moan; Fun (A: Drumly / Pleasure); Piano Trip
    - Title: Piano Trip (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2117)
      Related ID's: 152.2111-152.2116
      Related Titles: Latin (L); W Long Ravish; H Jazy (B: Scissors); Sax Moan; Fun (A: Drumly / Pleasure); Dont No / Pump Chaw
    - Title: Pointilism (L) (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2118)
    - Title: V. Rocking / Eros (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2119)
    - Title: Piano Bounce (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2120)
    - Title: Bell tune (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2121)
    - Title: Vocal Scale / Loop Train (A: Sex C) (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2122)
    - Title: Funk 1A (Box 2C.b, Folder ID: 152.2123)
    - Title: G. High Strain (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2124)
      Related ID's: 152.2125-152.2135
      Related Titles: Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto); G-triping; Mystry 2; Jog (B: Kazoo); Bounce (L); Epic / Gong (4); P-Sop (A: Dan 4); Funeral (A: Disappear); Trill; Baritone P. / Sop. Lo; Bambo / Tibet
    - Title: Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto) (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2125)
      Related ID's: 152.2124; 152.2126-152.2135
      Related Titles: G. High Strain; G-triping; Mystry 2; Jog (B: Kazoo); Bounce (L); Epic / Gong (4); P-Sop (A: Dan 4); Funeral (A: Disappear); Trill; Baritone P. / Sop. Lo; Bambo / Tibet
    - Title: G-triping (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2126)
      Related ID's: 152.2124-152.2125; 152.2127-152.2135
      Related Titles: G. High Strain; Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto); Mystry 2; Jog (B: Kazoo); Bounce (L); Epic / Gong (4); P-Sop (A: Dan 4); Funeral (A: Disappear); Trill; Baritone P. / Sop. Lo; Bambo / Tibet
    - Title: Mystry 2 (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2127)
      Related ID's: 152.2124-152.2126; 152.2128-152.2135
      Related Titles: G. High Strain; Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto); G-Triping; Jog (B: Kazoo); Bounce (L); Epic / Gong (4); P-Sop (A: Dan 4); Funeral (A: Disappear); Trill; Baritone P. / Sop. Lo; Bambo / Tibet
    - Title: Jog (B: Kazoo) (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2128)
      Related ID's: 152.2124-152.2127; 152.2129-152.2135
      Related Titles: G. High Strain; Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto); G-Triping; Mystry 2; Bounce (L); Epic / Gong (4); P-Sop (A: Dan 4); Funeral (A: Disappear); Trill; Baritone P. / Sop. Lo; Bambo / Tibet
    - Title: Bounce (L) (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2129)
      Related ID's: 152.2124-152.2128; 152.2130-152.2135
      Related Titles: G. High Strain; Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto); G-Triping; Mystry 2; Jog (B: Kazoo); Epic / Gong (4); P-Sop (A: Dan 4); Funeral (A: Disappear); Trill; Baritone P. / Sop. Lo; Bambo / Tibet
    - Title: Epic / Gong (4) (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2130)
      Related ID's: 152.2124-152.2129; 152.2131-152.2135
      Related Titles: G. High Strain; Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto); G-Triping; Mystry 2; Jog (B: Kazoo); Bounce (L); P-Sop (A: Dan 4); Funeral (A: Disappear); Trill; Baritone P. / Sop. Lo; Bambo / Tibet
    - Title: P-Sop (A: Dan 4) (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2131)
      Related ID's: 152.2124-152.2130; 152.2132-152.2135
      Related Titles: G. High Strain; Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto); G-Triping; Mystry 2; Jog (B: Kazoo); Bounce (L); Epic / Gong (4); Funeral (A: Disappear); Trill; Baritone P. / Sop. Lo; Bambo / Tibet
    - Title: Funeral (A: Disappear) (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2132)
      Related ID's: 152.2124-152.2131; 152.2133-152.2135
      Related Titles: G. High Strain; Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto); G-Triping; Mystry 2; Jog (B: Kazoo); Bounce (L); Epic / Gong (4); P-Sop (A: Dan 4); Trill; Baritone P. / Sop. Lo; Bambo / Tibet
      Tape Brand: Ampex Normal Bias 672 C-45
    - Title: Trill (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2133)
      Related ID's: 152.2124-152.2132; 152.2134-152.2135
      Related Titles: G. High Strain; Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto); G-Triping; Mystry 2; Jog (B: Kazoo); Bounce (L); Epic / Gong (4); P-Sop (A: Dan 4); Funeral (A: Disappear); Baritone P. / Sop. Lo; Bambo / Tibet
    - Title: Baritone P. / Sop. Lo (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2134)
      Related ID's: 152.2124-152.2133; 152.2135
      Related Titles: G. High Strain; Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto); G-Triping; Mystry 2; Jog (B: Kazoo); Bounce (L); Epic / Gong (4); P-Sop (A: Dan 4); Funeral (A: Disappear); Trill; Bambo / Tibet
    - Title: Bambo / Tibet (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2135)
      Related ID's: 152.2124-152.2134
      Related Titles: G. High Strain; Bt Weird (A: Chinese Sto); G-Triping; Mystry 2; Jog (B: Kazoo); Bounce (L); Epic / Gong (4); P-Sop (A: Dan 4); Funeral (A: Disappear); Trill; Baritone P. / Sop. Lo
    - Title: Jazz / Base Echo (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2136)
    - Title: V. Heart / Wist (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2137)
    - Title: Rotarun Tiny (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2138)
    - Title: E: Jolly (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2139)
    - Title: 15) Baratone / Disco (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2140)
    - Title: Jazz (A: Chemical war? / Chatter) (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2141)
    - Title: Sufi 1 (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2142)
    - Title: Brf Violin (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2143)
    - Title: Piano gay (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2144)
    - Title: Pleasure Saw (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2145)
    - Title: Pleasure Dip (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2146)
    - Title: G: Up-Down F (Box 2C.c, Folder ID: 152.2147)
    - Title: Unch / Lite (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2148)
    - Title: Locust / Drumgun (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2149)
    - Title: Cornfield (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2150)
    - Title: Base Strum (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2151)
    - Title: Trouble / Sax (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2152)
      Tape Brand: TDK Normal Bias D30
    - Title: Wltz (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2153)
    - Title: P. Dance (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2154)
    - Title: Nitetown (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2155)
    - Title: Drum / Steel (A: [Fem?] Voice B) (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2156)
    - Title: March M / Sop (A: Sweet / Aria) (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2157)
    - Title: Swings (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2158)
    - Title: M Train (A: Fast Chip / Cheer) (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2159)
      Tape Brand: Philips Type I Normal Bias Ferro C60
    - Title: Ranch-St (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2160)
    - Title: Twang (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2161)
    - Title: China (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2162)
    - Title: Toot (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2163)
    - Title: Bach 4 / Veronica (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2164)
    - Title: [Label removed] (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2165)
    - Title: Hawaii (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2166)
    - Title: Horns (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2167)
    - Title: Trot (L) (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2168)
    - Title: Turandot / Goof (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2169)
    - Title: Bell tune (11) Bounce (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2170)
    - Title: Weird (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2171)
    - Title: Base Pluck (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2172)
    - Title: Monroe Groan (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2173)
    - Title: Slo Bleat / Slo Warn (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2174)
    - Title: Rhythm Sq. / R. Umph 35 (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2175)
    - Title: Rota whirl (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2176)
    - Title: Rota brass (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2177)
    - Title: Lalo - steps (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2178)
    - Title: Chug (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2179)
    - Title: Sop Ch[ild?] (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2180)
    - Title: Strings - St (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2181)
    - Title: Gongs (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2182)
    - Title: Welch (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2183)
    - Title: Rota groan (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2184)
    - Title: Intro (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2185)
    - Title: Lava start (A: Opening lava) (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2186)
    - Title: Cha Cha (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2187)
    - Title: Kreisler (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2188)
    - Title: Beats (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2189)
    - Title: Ring (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2190)
    - Title: Jig (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2191)
    - Title: Piano Hicks (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2192)
    - Title: Pump Chaw (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2193)
    - Title: Organ (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2194)
      Tape Brand: Ampex Plus Series
    - Title: Checko (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2195)
    - Title: Trill / Brf. Violin (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2196)
    - Title: Sop Round / Hi Sop (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2197)
    - Title: Popsi / Mellow (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2198)
    - Title: Monrow 6-6 (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2199)
    - Title: Faure 3 (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2200)
    - Title: Jolly / Base (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2201)
    - Title: Rock: trill-slo (A: Indian) (B: Play 6) (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2202)
    - Title: Lalo: gloom (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2203)
    - Title: E Scale (Box 3A, Folder ID: 152.2204)
    - Title: Lala: Jig (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2205)
    - Title: Tex Loop (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2206)
    - Title: Rhythm Bells / V. Loop (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2207)
    - Title: Hips (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2208)
    - Title: Lalo: Oar (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2209)
    - Title: Lalo: sweet (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2210)
    - Title: Lalo: Vase (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2211)
    - Title: Blast (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2212)
    - Title: Rainwood (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2213)
    - Title: Moan / Popsi (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2214)
    - Title: Talk / June Fst Clear (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2215)
      Tape Brand: Sony High Bias UX
    - Title: Turando 1 / Blurp (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2216)
    - Title: Hi Sop / L org (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2217)
    - Title: Orch Flair (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2218)
    - Title: Violin / John Doodle (A: Arab Beat) (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2219)
    - Title: Sq Dance (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2220)
    - Title: Sop 2 (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2221)
    - Title: Hello Sailor (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2222)
    - Title: Gersh 2 (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2223)
    - Title: Sax Moan / Fst Pluck (A: Bacl S) (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2224)
    - Title: Goof (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2225)
    - Title: Drum: Mellow (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2226)
    - Title: Ahh (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2227)
    - Title: Ply - Cords (A: SH) (B: Keep [the?] Ball Rolling) (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2228)
    - Title: Clarnet (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2229)
    - Title: Grump (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2230)
    - Title: Tuba (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2231)
    - Title: Rota twitch (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2232)
    - Title: L: Cut / Chico (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2233)
    - Title: Garble (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2234)
    - Title: Blare (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2235)
    - Title: Lalo: Pendule (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2236)
    - Title: Lalo: Sad (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2237)
    - Title: Lalo: doubt (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2238)
    - Title: Clucker (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2239)
    - Title: P. Weird / Rumba (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2240)
    - Title: Soprano (A: Highly Build. / Harm. Tone and Coral?) (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2241)
    - Title: Bop Drum (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2242)
    - Title: 2 Tone (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2243)
    - Title: Mystic / Turandot #10 (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2244)
    - Title: Loopy (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2245)
    - Title: Song of Jack (B: NR) (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2246)
    - Title: Lalo: Voc (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2247)
    - Title: Dog Growl (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2248)
    - Title: Disco A / Bees (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2249)
    - Title: Bach Org / Slo Warn #11 (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2250)
    - Title: Lalo: Sigh (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2251)
    - Title: Lalo: Bara (Box 3B, Folder ID: 152.2252)
    - Title: Squeeze / Numbers (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2253)
    - Title: Chug / Columbus (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2254)
    - Title: Bach Violence (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2255)
    - Title: Death / O Saw (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2256)
    - Title: Org (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2257)
    - Title: Flute (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2258)
    - Title: (A: Barkina) (B: Pencil) (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2259)
    - Title: Train blare (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2260)
    - Title: Ache (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2261)
    - Title: Swoops (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2262)
    - Title: Glock / I Don't Know (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2263)
      Tape Brand: Philips Ferro Low Noise C-60
    - Title: V 1/2 / V Slo (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2264)
    - Title: Babble / CZ (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2265)
    - Title: E Yearn (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2266)
    - Title: Chekos (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2267)
    - Title: Drum Speed (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2268)
    - Title: JJ Jungle / Roll / Add Drum Paradiddle Accent (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2269)
      Tape Brand: ESIC Hi-Fi Low Noise C-60
    - Title: Bable Music (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2270)
    - Title: Violin / Mystic (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2271)
    - Title: Melancholy (A: USA) (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2272)
    - Title: Drum Roll (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2273)
    - Title: Garble (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2274)
    - Title: Checkos / Stk Lump (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2275)
    - Title: Lalo: Burp (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2276)
    - Title: Gargle / Bongo (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2277)
    - Title: Sop Insist / Mon Xylo (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2278)
    - Title: Rinky (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2279)
    - Title: Chucks (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2280)
    - Title: Chigs (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2281)
    - Title: Jump (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2282)
    - Title: E: Runs (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2283)
    - Title: Bnjo Ping (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2284)
    - Title: Strum (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2285)
    - Title: G Strings (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2286)
    - Title: Org Mic / Org 1/2 (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2287)
    - Title: Bach Org / Ossil (2) (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2288)
    - Title: Orch Slo / 1-2-3-4 (A: Harmon Tone) (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2289)
    - Title: Violin / Big Girl (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2290)
    - Title: 2 Pling (A: Fog + Plunkit) (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2291)
    - Title: Monk Hits / Gnome (B: Trugs) (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2292)
    - Title: Vocal Yearn (A: Laf / See Saw) (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2293)
    - Title: Pdle Org (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2294)
    - Title: Tootle (A: Monk Whine / Sop Xcent) (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2295)
    - Title: Beat Groans (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2296)
    - Title: Groans (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2297)
    - Title: Violin fst / Violin Fever / Chros (A: Fem A / Fem B) (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2298)
    - Title: J.J. Xmas (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2299)
    - Title: Sop Haha / Rumba (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2300)
    - Title: Stock: Bounce (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2301)
    - Title: Sop Round / Hi Sop (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2302)
    - Title: Maha / Opera (9) (A: Mystic / Mystic Ch) (Box 3C, Folder ID: 152.2303)
    - Title: Dum-Dum (A: Float) (B: Falsetto / Geson) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2304)
    - Title: Geson / Sunny (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2305)
    - Title: Lalo Choral (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2306)
    - Title: Lalo: Sing (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2307)
    - Title: Activity (A: Rota [W…?]) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2308)
    - Title: Brisk - Long (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2309)
    - Title: Hollow / Piano (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2310)
    - Title: V-Note [Lalo: flute] (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2311)
    - Title: Slow Strum (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2312)
    - Title: Cooko (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2313)
    - Title: Hottentot / Edit (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2314)
    - Title: V Check (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2315)
    - Title: Lovely (A: Tibet fast) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2316)
    - Title: Laping (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2317)
    - Title: V. Grave / Fats (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2318)
    - Title: Rota Waltzy (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2319)
    - Title: Dan / Hits (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2320)
    - Title: Toots (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2321)
    - Title: Branca (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2322)
    - Title: Violin Chinese (A: Sex E) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2323)
    - Title: Hindoo (A: Yid: Whirl) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2324)
    - Title: P Vamp (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2325)
    - Title: Me / Bird Slo (23) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2326)
    - Title: Cho Cho Bang (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2327)
    - Title: E - Chase (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2328)
    - Title: Pluck (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2329)
    - Title: Org Warp / A / B (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2330)
    - Title: Wild Bt / Org. Gyrate (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2331)
    - Title: 5) Sop / Sweet (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2332)
    - Title: E: Trill (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2333)
    - Title: Org: Starter (A: Slo Drum) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2334)
    - Title: Face / 123 (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2335)
    - Title: Bride to Be (B: Instrumental) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2336)
    - Title: Tight (L) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2337)
    - Title: P Rocking / Zum Zum (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2338)
    - Title: Minuete (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2339)
    - Title: Bongo (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2340)
    - Title: Insist (B: Masters) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2341)
    - Title: Deep (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2342)
    - Title: Wobble Drum (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2343)
    - Title: Whiz Bang (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2344)
    - Title: Lalo: Aria (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2345)
    - Title: Zips (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2346)
    - Title: Slow Stroke (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2347)
    - Title: Drum=Taps (A: Sway B) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2348)
    - Title: John (B: Drum Pure) (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2349)
    - Title: Hit Clk (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2350)
    - Title: Zips (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2351)
    - Title: Tuba Chug 2B (Box 3D., Folder ID: 152.2352)
    - Title: Org Test (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2353)
    - Title: Whine (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2354)
    - Title: (A: Malher - Bus Long) (B: Mahler Bus fst.) (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2355)
    - Title: Busoni - Osil (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2356)
    - Title: Bone (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2357)
    - Title: Mex 2 [agg.?] (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2358)
    - Title: Bus P strum (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2359)
    - Title: Filibet (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2360)
    - Title: Rub Dub (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2361)
    - Title: Mex Joly (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2362)
    - Title: Bus. Groan (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2363)
    - Title: Dp P. (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2364)
    - Title: 3 cool chicks (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2365)
    - Title: Chord (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2366)
    - Title: Cha Cha (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2367)
    - Title: Strm (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2368)
    - Title: Bus Groan (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2369)
    - Title: Rap Mex (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2370)
    - Title: Bus: "L" (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2371)
    - Title: Nomi (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2372)
    - Title: Calipoe (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2373)
    - Title: [untitled] (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2374)
    - Title: Shiver (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2375)
    - Title: Mex 1 (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2376)
    - Title: Mid East (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2377)
    - Title: Strm (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2378)
    - Title: Making Change Easy / Releasing The Blocks to Positive Core Level Change / This Soundtrack Uses The Patented Silent Subliminal Technology (Box MK, Folder ID: 152.2379)
      Tape Brand: Holosync BASF CrO2
  - Subseries C: Video Recordings - Access Copies